Overcomer Emiator

A passionate Programmer

Benin

xceldeveloper@gmail.com

+234 815 869 6460

Hi, I am a passionate developer with good experience designing Webapps, Blogs, Android Apps, Opensource Projects etc utilizing varieties of Software Technologies which include Vuejs, Nuxt, Flutter, Nodejs, Django, JQuery, Tailwindcss, Scss, Git

I have experience working remotely building meaningful and productive software with also the ability to work with minimal supervision as I have the zeal to tackle any problems I might encounter independently to achieve the desired result.

Work Experience

Frontend Developer

Scelloo - Lagos February 2021 to Present

Frontend Developer at Scelloo (SaaS Company) exercising my Vuejs and Tailwindcss skills in building its Software

Frontend Developer (Contract)

Mulaa Analytics and Technology - Lagos November 2021 to January 2022

Helping in improving and building new features for their on-going startup project

Frontend Developer (Consultant)

Archub

November 2021 to November 2021

I basically was asked to help out with a feature the company frontend developers where having implementing. This was a Vuejs project

Frontend Developer (Contract)

Connectivo - Sweden August 2021 to October 2021

Frontend Developer (Contract)

Nodens Nigeria Limited - Lagos August 2021 to September 2021

Contact Job to build nodtransfer.com using Vuejs and Vuetify

Frontend Developer

Celcic Media - Lagos August 2020 to February 2021

Frontend Developer utilizing my Vuejs expertise

Frontend Developer (Part time)

2GFields - Benin

October 2019 to March 2020

Per time Developer at 2GFields (Software Company) as a Frontend Developer

Education

B.Sc in Mathematics

University of Benin - Nigeria

October 2016 to August 2021

Skills

- JavaScript (4 years)
- JQuery (3 years)
- Java (2 years)
- Vuejs (3 years)
- Nuxtjs (2 years)
- Nodejs (1 year)
- Kotlin (1 year)
- Tailwindcss
- Django (1 year)
- Flutter (1 year)
- SCSS
- Git
- Front-End Development (4 years)
- Node.js
- GitHub
- Googling
- HTML5
- Web development
- REST
- UI
- CSS3

Languages

• English - Fluent

Links

http://linkedin.com/in/overcomer-emiator-5573141b2/

https://github.com/xceldeveloper

https://twitter.com/xceldeveloper

https://xceldeveloper.com

Assessments

Attention to detail — Proficient

February 2021

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information

Full results: Proficient

Software developer skills — Familiar

March 2021

Designed by engineering managers and real-world employers, this test gives you hard data points to evaluate technical competency

Full results: Familiar

Software developer fit — Proficient

July 2021

Measures the traits that are important for successful software developers

Full results: Proficient

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Publications

vue-device-detector-js

https://www.npmjs.com/package/vue-device-detector-js

January 2021

A vuejs plugin for the client device detection

vue-theme-manager

https://www.npmjs.com/package/vue-theme-manager

March 2021

A vuejs plugin for Managing theme(s) colors in the whole of your Vue web app. It has support for Vue 2 and Vue 3